<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_App">Welcome to Tic Tac Toe! From the main menu, you can either start a game, open up the records, or edit the two players. There are four games to play, you can find the directions for them by swiping.</string>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_Hangman">The hangman game has two games you can swipe between. Each player uses one game to think of a word for the other to guess. Once you think of your word hit \'send\' and let the other person think of their word. Then you take turns guessing.</string>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_TicTacToe">By tapping the face icon at the bottom, you can toggle between playing against the computer and playing against each other, and you can swipe to play multiple games at the same time. Other than that the game is tic tac toe- try to get three in a row. </string>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_SuperTicTacToe">This game you may not have played before. I have heard it called Ultimate Tic Tac Toe, but I prefer Super Tic Tac Toe as this name does not misuse the word \'ultimate\'. \nThe goal of this game is the same in regular tic tac toe- get three in a row, but rather than three x\'s or o\'s, you have to win three games in a row. Where you go in a particular game sends the next player to the tic tac toe game that corresponds to where you just moved. If that corresponding game is already over then every other game opens up. \nThe brighter tiles are the potential moves, once you win a tic tac toe game those tiles are shaded in your color. </string>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_SuperTicTacToeHangman">As far as I know, this game does not exist outside of this app, it was devised by two high school students during their computer science class (one of them developed this app). \nIt functions very similarly to super tic tac toe, and should only be played once that game is understood. \nEach player has a hang man game that they play instead of one of the tic tac toe games. If you get sent to your own hangman game, then you go to the other one so you can actually guess a letter. If you guess incorrectly, then the entire board opens up. If you guess correctly then you choose which board opens up for the other player. \nThere are directions at the top to facilitate playing. The game cannot begin before the players choose their words. I recommend just playing through and getting a feel for the rules.</string>
    <string name="DIRECTIONS_Records">To search for your game records, simply type your name and tap \'get record\'. Capitalization matters, but trailing spaces do not.\nThe switches at the bottom allow you to delete records. If  you turn 2 or 3 on, then you can delete a player\'s game history. If you switch all four on, you can get rid of all game history. \nThese records are stored on your device, and your device only- nothing is backed up, so be careful with deleting because you cannot get it back!</string>
</resources>